Hello Hello friend, welcome to our
YouTube channel named Rahul Jain
Vishwas Guru. So friends, today we are going to talk in
this video
about the plan which
gives you unlimited restoration benefit,
meaning that if you take Someshwar of 10 lakhs, then
you can get the benefit of any problem up to one crore.
How will we
talk about the plan? We will talk about how
we can increase
Play
Services from 10 lakhs to 20 lakhs in the next three years under the booster benefit, that is, no claim bonus in this plan. So
please watch this video
completely, as you are
getting information about which plan in the market
gives you unlimited restoration benefit. So friends,
if you have not subscribed to this channel, then
subscribe quickly. Press the bell icon so
that you get complete
notifications. You get notifications of videos on time.
As you
can grow our insurance advisory business by watching videos. If
you are a member of any  There is acid with any company, if you are doing
business
with any insurance company by
taking your health insurance code or doing
business with life insurance on Friday, then
friends, definitely subscribe to this channel
so that you will get
knowledge about many products, I am going to tell you
how you
can earn money in insurance business by selling different codes in different companies under Insurance Advisor, soft, let's
start and I will tell you
what benefits you are going to get in Max's Real Power Play,
soft, as I
told you, the rear of repair and the
line above,
you get unlimited restoration benefit in it, which
means that if you took a plan, then if you took
10 lakhs, when the pure
silk gets over, it gives you 10 lakhs again without any
cost, and if 10 lakhs are
over, it gives 10 lakhs again, there is
no cost again, which means that in one year you
can avail the benefit of unlimited registrations.
You can get unlimited registrations by doing 10 plus 10 plus 10 plus plus, so
you get a unique feature in this product of
Amazon. Let's talk about the
booster benefit here, if you remember, if you
heard about the no claim bonus, then the no
claim bonus is also our booster benefit,
meaning that today if I take a policy of 10 lakhs and do
not make any claim for one year, then
if I am going to get a no claim bonus of 50% here,
if you have a policy of 10 lakhs, then
in the next year also the policy of 15 lakhs will be available, if
I clear the second year then in the third year I get a
combination of grinding, the
second benefit is related to some different
benefits, which are related to health checkup,
now in this plan you
get the benefit of health checkup from Devon, although you
will try the suggestion in the market, there is a
benefit of health checkup, the benefit of routine health
checkup is available in some complete,
after 2 years, after 3 years or even
after 4 years in the market  It is available
but here Max Bupa, that is,
it is giving you its benefit from Devon,
so this is an additional
benefit to you, you can sell the product by using this benefit here,
now let's talk about
some additional benefits which are option
benefits, you can avail it if you live alone,
but it is covered under the de-save features award feature
like discount on non-verbal items,
apart from this all the other consumable items are
covered here,
however in this video we
will talk about what is cut benefit,
apart from this live health benefit means that if you have
taken an insurance plan and along with this
you exercise yourself to stay fit, do
some activities for yourself, do
some yoga etc.
then here the company has given you a discount of up to 30 percent
and at the time of
renewal you have an
option that you can avail renewal benefit of up to 30 percent by staying fit from the company.
Okay, so here
you are given an application of a company,
all those things are tracked through it,
now let's talk about 30-minute
cashless approval, that is, your approval is done in
30 minutes, if
you have taken Nibha's health insurance product,
if all your documentation and all the
things are complete here,
you get approved here within 10:30 in the morning,
so this is a good thing for you because
many of the customers face
problem in completing the process by clicking on the time, it
often takes 2 hours, 8 hours or even the whole
day to approve and present it, but please
comment on the company here because
we used to provide it to you within 2 to 3 minutes
and you get its benefits here, we will
talk about some of its amazing
benefits, like in this product
we are talking about yes and now what are the
benefits and
things inside the rear and the company, let's talk about this
separately, this first  There used to be Max Bupa, now it is
Nibhaoge, so I have already told you that this
company is named Nibha, this is a low
principal benefit, in this you get unlimited benefits,
restoration as we are
saying and apart from this
you can cover hospital expenses,
you can take width treatment here under this policy,
then thirdly
if we talk about this here
you can increase your benefits on seven different glasses, like
for ten lakh attempts you get 10 lakhs, here you
get restoration benefit, 10 lakhs,
you
get registration benefit of 10 lakhs, so here
your unlimited is such that your benefit keeps
increasing, this is called basic,
always
it will be called restoration benefits
statement show here, for if you
take it here then your basic here, which
you used for any one disease, then
some companies do
not give you rescission benefit on one disease, so
you can increase your insurance here on the same disease or on different diseases  But
you can avail the benefit of the policy here without any additional cost.
If I have used this as a basic disease, then
this thing called restoration benefit can also be used for
one disease twice, I can
use it for the same disease. Here
many companies do not give
you the benefit of using sum assured for this particular disease, they do
not give you the benefit of registration,
but in this you
can discover some sum assured, Vijay you
can avail the benefit in this. Now let's talk about
some companies here, they promise you,
because on time, like here multiple
customers get the benefit here in this policy,
otherwise if you have
taken a policy product here, then you
also got more network hospitals, okay, here
you go to network hospitals,
apart from this multiple sums benefits, here
you also get different financial benefits,
we will talk about that
in the middle of this presentation.
Apart from this, friends, I will talk about your
Idli, if you are an eligible member, you
want to see how it works.  I am
looking for it for metro cities in Delhi NCR, you want to other
set for this, the
setting for remotest is shown here, you can take the plan for the
offspring, meaning if I
want to take a plan for myself alone, then I can take it for
12210, if I
want to add a child with you, then that can be one
plus two for 1310, meaning I can
insure myself alone in the team along with four
children, here to get it eligible under the policy, I am
telling you in a condition here, how
can you suggest a family here, if it has
any six children and
normal husband, wife, interested students,
you will see any new plan of Congress
and what all can you do, you can do OnePlus 3 quality, you
can do OnePlus 3 quality, we will
point to the side and send it, then you
can go inside this option, right, to
explain, let me tell you
what we can do, if someone has
more children in his family members,
then how can we cover them  Yes,
here the total means that you can take husband-wife policy,
husband-wife one child
policy, but you should have taken her husband back
to my channel,
friend circle, then this is your pimple condition,
if I talk about members,
you can find it in the same way,
if you look for OnePlus One
more
subscribed member, there are
many other things like now let's talk,
first of all we will talk about here,
you get support from now till 1 crore, in some remote
areas you get support of 3 lakhs,
if you are from metro city then
you will not get this plan below 5 lakhs,
so if you talk about MS Word then you
cannot leave the time between 5 lakhs to 1 crore,
for modern treatment,
you get subvention up to one lakh in this plan,
if you have taken insurance of 10 lakhs, then
for modern treatment,
you can cover treatment up to 1 lakh only in it, now let's
talk about air ambulance, air
ambulance covers you, that means if
someone's need  A critical situation arises
after going to a hilly area or
in some situation
where you need an air ambulance or a
helicopter, then you
can pay for it from your pocket from the company and
can avail a time injury benefit of up to Rs 2.5 lakh and can claim restoration and this
is famous from these reports of the whole year,
meaning that if you use it throughout the year, then
you can avail the full benefit till the end of the year.
Friends, we were
talking about air ambulance, hundred percent
coverage, hundred percent coverage means
that under this policy, your
consumer electronics or any other
expenses like how to avoid
taxes, all of them become yours.
If you take some additional benefits,
extra benefits, then
you get covered under this policy. The
meaning of tractor on this mission is that
as you can see, there is
an index of the government.  This is a C prank, so
within the index, if the government can
declare that our five percent
inflation, you can
also increase your time of your policy
through inflation index, okay, so
if the government declares your 5 percent, if
you take a plan of Rs 10 lakh, then your
time will increase by Rs 50,000, it will never
decrease because you have
given additional money for the intake, this traditional feature,
you have to do it on this platform, it is a time
waste, we will talk about it later, it
works in this way,
suppose if you have taken a plan and it
takes it up to Rs 50,000 within the whole year, then the
claim benefit of the booster benefit, the
no claim bonus, will not be included there, so
if you take additional benefits, booster
benefits, then here you will get a claim of Rs 50,000
and you will
get the benefit of Bluetooth, we will talk about it later, this is the
way this thing works, so it is
below you  Those who have health benefits, some
additional benefits from your normal pain, you can get
treatment, that is,
if you want to take treatment, then here the
company tells you, so olive oil to
kabaddi medical treatment expenses taken at
home as advised by the medical
practitioner, that is, if the doctor
suggests you that you can
take home treatment, then in home treatment, there are
some conditions in it, like
your situation is either not suitable for treatment, it is a
critical situation, or there is a problem in the hospital,
or if the doctor advises you to
take fitness for more than three days, stay at home, then
you can take your treatment at home,
within the commitment, thanks, and we will talk about the remaining medicines,
what is basically there in the medicine, there are some limits here,
as you were seeing, the limits are different
on the basis of the Someshwar mode of, we will
talk about this,
how is the presentation coming next, let's talk about the
second medical  Opinion: Okay, suppose
I have a plan and I have a critical
situation, I have some disease
for which I
need to consult a doctor immediately,
if I share all the documents and reports with the company, I can avail
second
opinion benefit from the company here, I can consult the doctor as to
how many days it will take to treat a particular disease, how cheaply,
in which hospital, in what amount,
so
you get all these benefits inside the account opening,
select Enter Benefit on Optional, this option
benefits that if you
want to take Central Benefit along with your quality, then
you get the benefit here which is
five times the basic possible or
your maximum up to one
crore is okay, if you have 10 lakh APR
then maximum five will have to be done, for the first
time in the morning, then you will get benefit up to 50 lakh on 10 lakh
or if you have taken a plan of 20 lakh then
you can avail this benefit up to one crore.  You
can avail the benefit here under the accidental policy. This is an additional feature; you may have to pay
extra for it. Let us
know what are the benefits within the product's benefits.
Answer, as I mentioned
starting with Buddha Tilak, it provides you with
intolerance up to Rs 1 crore.
Under Doctor Spring, you
can see it. Apart from this, the
benefits that are covered here, up
to Someshwar, what is the benefit within the policy? Infection
treatment means the
treatment you get in the hospital, related to it is room
rent, ICU, doctor's fee, consultation,
medicine, or any reports. If you are
admitted in the hospital for more than 24 hours under infection treatment, then you
can avail the treatment of all these things under in-patient care.
Now let's talk about our treatment.
Like the Mishri treatment that I mentioned,
if the doctor requests that
you stay at home for more than three days
and avail its benefit, then
you can also avail the benefit of home treatment here.
Now let's talk about  Day
treatment: If,
due to technological advancement, there
is a treatment in which you don't have to stay in the hospital for 24 hours,
you can get treatment within 2 hours, 3 hours,
4 hours and
come back home, then such treatment is also
covered by the company. Should examine this
policy and you get cover. Apart from this,
you get cover on donuts here, like
I gave you home treatment for example,
although it is written twice, so
auditor's treatment means that in the East
we call it your Unani, Siddha,
Ayurvedic treatment, all these
things come under iPod treatment, so you
also get cover for alternative treatment up to a certain period under this product. If you have
taken a plan of 5 lakhs, then you get cover up to 5 lakhs and
terminated treatment, if you have taken a plan of 10 lakhs, then you will get cover up to 10
lakhs. We
will talk about living organ donor.
Living organ donor, if someone's
organ gets damaged, someone
needs a kidney transplant or someone
needs a liver transplant or there is any other organ
problem, then you can arrange for
organ transfer under this line.  You can take the benefit,
here you get
organ transfer benefit of up to two problems inside this plan, we will
talk about booster
benefit here, booster benefit, I told you
that if you do not take any benefit
within the whole year, you get 50% no claim
bonus on top of the basic deposit,
which you get in the whole year, maximum
of 200 percent, if you have
10 lakhs then 20 lakhs will go in the mix, if you have 5
lakhs then maximum 10 lakhs will go, in
this way you get placement up to 100 percent,
apart from this, there is
also a need to understand the reduction here, if
my policy is increasing in no claim bonus then
how will it reduce, okay, if I take a claim then
how will it reduce, if a policy of 10 lakhs is
not claimed then it becomes 15, after 15 lakhs it becomes
second, if I join again then the
reduction will remain from 15 to 10,
but that basic benefit will not always go below,
if I have taken 10 lakhs as basic, then it will be
below 10 lakhs  I will
not understand that that particular sum is low, the
premium should be paid by the company, here
what was there in the life health benefits which
I told you that if you
want a discount of up to 30% at the time of renewal, then here
you have to deduct some points from the company's health points,
like if you exercise,
you do activities, Yogesh etc. then there is a
mobile application of another company, through that
you can track everything, your
things will be tracked, your activities will be tracked
and after that, if you want a contingent of 30% at the time of renewal, then
you can take this 30% discount up to 30
% from the company, now let's talk about
some other additional benefits like there is
medicine cash, but if suppose
today you
want to see the benefit of medicine, then
you have taken any insurance plan in which
you are eligible for single room, but
in the hospital you say that Singh Arun milk is
not available, then you have taken a shadow combination,
take a daring form  If you have taken it,
what benefit does the company give you in it that you can get up to Rs 215 off to Rs 15 lakh and
if you have taken a policy with a benefit of up to Rs 15 lakh, then
you will get a benefit of Rs 800, maximum Rs 48
from the office or if you have
taken a policy for more than Rs 15 lakh, then you will get a
benefit of Rs 1000, which gives you a maximum benefit of Rs 6000, we will talk about the
second medical option and 9
opinions here also, although I had told you
that if you want to cut any holidays, you can take these options from the company,
if you sell the company
and want to get that card benefit, then you
can take the second option,
you can see its benefit from the company, then there is an account
opening benefit, under modern treatment
you
get the benefit of treatment up to Rs 1 lakh, there is a particular sub-limit, you will
get benefit above this, like if you have
undergone robotic surgery, for example, if you
see that the therapist etc. all these
things are covered under this plan till the time of wish  Let's
talk about the mode of the center, what are the
things that we can cover under add-on benefits,
like seat benefits. Let's
understand what seat benefits are.
Under the SIM card benefit, first of all,
if I want to cover non-table item control system,
then I
can cover consumable items under Shivkant, like your
picket, your glass, your cotton,
whatever kind of items you have, all those
things are covered under your savings. Don't
pay a little extra premium along with the pallu, for
all your things, and there is booster
benefit, meaning if you have taken up to 50,000, then
in that case, you will not have any effect here on
your booster benefit, that is, for a
plan of 50,000, as told earlier,
your no claim bonus will
not be added in the name of 50,000, and along with that, you will get a
claim of up to 5,000 here. If the
next amount is below 50,000, then this benefit refers to you and
you will get the benefit.  It goes
in the name of Swift that you have agreed,
then you will get it. Apart from this, there is a
CPI index which is a government
contract, so if you
see the information in it, the government does
five percent cancellation, then
inside your policy also there will be an increase of 45 percent,
which will
not happen if you make a claim, your
infection will keep increasing, on S, the government
and acts, okay, so under the C index
you get this benefit, let's
talk about hospital cash quantity,
if you have taken up to 5 minutes for admission in the hospital, then
you get admission in the hospital for Rs. 1000,
this is also an additional don't feature, you will have to do
white for this, let's understand seven and a half lakh to
15 lakh, then you
can take a hospital cash account of up to ₹2000,
many people do jobs, do business,
so friends, if I fall
ill somewhere, then I am not able to go to work, I am not able to
go in between  So I am incurring a loss,
okay, so to recover that loss,
you can go to a financier here,
as I had also visited the Plan Center,
financial benefits, so it will
work like a final benefit for you,
suppose for 10 days
for treatment in the hospital and you have spent 10 lakh rupees,
then you will get 2000 rupees as benefit here,
you will have to pay extra for it, there is an add don't don't
feature, okay, so
here you will get extra 20 thousand rupees
if you are admitted in the hospital for 10 days,
okay, if the sum is above 15 lakh rupees,
you will have to pay 4000 rupees, you will get the
benefit, let's talk about this
problem picture inside this plan, this is also an
advanced feature, for this you have to
play extract PM, this personal
accidental cover, if you want to take Section Jal Cover
policy with your base policy,
you will get five times when someone gets
10 lakh rupees
If you have it then you will get a maximum of Rs 50 lakh or you can take the maximum off.
Suppose you have taken a policy of Rs 50 lakh
and you want to get a five-time policy of Rs 2.5
crore, then you will not get a dental cover with it,
you will get the benefit only up to a maximum of Rs 1 crore.
Friends,
if you want to take the benefit of these features by giving extra credit, then
you can take the benefit of this credit with your best
policy. Friends, let me
talk about some meeting kidneys here like the
waiting period. I have already
told you earlier that while taking a first time job policy, there is a
waiting period for TDS.
You do not get a normal claim before 30 days.
Accept that you get any
injury due to an accident. If you get any
injury due to an accident, morning sickness and
apart from this, you want to get treatment for any disease immediately.
Third, after this, let's
talk about your cover. Two years
existing policy for some
specific diseases.  It happens like if you have a hernia, a
stone, a stroke, a joint
replacement, etc., okay, there are
15-16 digits like this, which the company covers you after 2 years. If
you take a plan for the
first time under any product, under any company, then
these diseases are
covered after 24 years, that is, after 2 years. Now let's talk about existing diseases.
If you already have
any disease, you have taken any treatment, you have any
problem, then you should declare it to the company
while taking the policy, then there is
a meeting for it, which is for three years.
In this particular plan,
if you declare to the company that you had an
operation three years ago, 10 years ago,
whether it is related to stone, then the
company will cover you for the stone which you were getting
covered after two years. Now, we will
cover your problem of that stone after three years. Let
me tell you that if you
declare it, then tomorrow there will be
no problem while taking the claim. So the better thing is that
when  If you also have a
problem like this, someone is undergoing treatment,
you have diabetes, you have a Tuesday
problem, you have any problem, suppose you have any
kind of asthma problem, you have any
problem, then like a customer, you should make this clear to the company
while taking the policy, then at the
time of claim itself you will
not have to fight for everything, your claim is
not going to be rejected, so let's talk about some
such benefits which the company never covers,
which we can call explosions,
half an inch, Adidas company never covers,
like ghee, if your OPD treatment is done,
you want to see a normal doctor
for cough and cold, and you want to charge the company for it, then
you will
not get its benefits here, let's talk about those
proper treatment or neglected
stitch 9 doctor or hospital, if you
went to a doctor in a hospital
which was not authorized by the government and got
your treatment done there and you
want to avail its benefits, then you have not got those benefits, let's say
you are not going to get them
Whenever you break any government rule in the beach or fruit and
you break any kind of rule
or if there is any disaster, any
fight, quarrel or any evil eye falls on all your things, then the
benefit that you will not get there will
not be vacated. If you are
related to adventure sports
or are doing any such activities like
paragliding or river rafting,
if you get any injury in such activities, then the
company will not make that claim here on particular
tracks and such disease which is
power distribution. You can talk about
change, you can get treatment related to gender
or you want hormone treatment,
replacement related things, you will get description of all these things,
plastic surgery, cosmetic
surgery is not available here on date.
Apart from this, if you have
any treatment like addiction, Salim or alcohol-related, then the
company will not cover you here,
as many people often drink
and drive, they drive after
drinking and there is an accident in it, then
there  But you will not get
flights to make in Play and
whenever you are telling the customer about the plan, then
what are the features along with this, also
tell that sir why this thing will not be covered for you,
along with which buildings, you should
also discuss about that
under Vanshlochan on 100, like dental diseases are
not covered for you, infertility and
maternity cover are not covered for you,
apart from this, if you talk about HIV
related section transplant unit of
it is a rapid, you will not discover it,
apart from this you will see that if I
want to go outside India and get my treatment done, if
this is some such problem then it is saying that you have a
mental disorder or
you have some problem related to neuro-development
or if you have attempted
suicide, then you face
any problem related to this, then all those
things are never
covered in the complete insurance claim, so friends, you must have understood these things, there will be
many things related to investment,
after this presentation
I told you  Tell me one thing in detail that
inside Max, inside God, which has been played,
what are the benefits you get in this plant, what are the
advanced features that you can take, you
can explain to the turtle, many
people open messages and send that they have adventures
in some company or the other and I too have some
adventures which are with me,
growing the business with me, generating my income,
so here let me tell you
that after this presentation, you would have roughly understood at least
80 things
that how we have to
give presentation to the client, finally you people will have
questions that sir you have explained
but if I want to make this presentation, I
want to explain the point, then how should I
make my presentation, so
friends, I have brought a good thing for you, this is
that there is
no need to make this presentation, what you can do
after watching this video, as you
go to the description below, on the description
you will get a copy of this presentation,
you can click on it  After clicking on your copy,
this presentation will be edited in your Google Drive, its additive
Scorpio will go in which you
can put your logo, you can do your branding,
you
can generate your list by making a YouTube video by putting your name and number on it, you
can also put it on any social media and use it for two qualities of presentation or if you
want to give a presentation to a client, want to make some changes,
you
can do all those things on your Android because
I am giving this prepaid plan to you people as a gift, I am
giving it to you as a benefit
and in the same way, in the upcoming
videos, we are going to show you this type of BTS and
tell you
what are the features in the health insurance, if you go for any product,
then subscribe to our channel right now,
press the bell icon on the channel, as you get the notification,
you get to know how we can
see the presentation, by explaining to the client, we
can increase our insurance verification work, we can get the money, finally I will
say if you have any  If you have
any variations to the question, please comment.
Go to the comment section and comment. If
you want to pass something on to my team or
discuss something with me,
you'll find our number in the description.
You can contact us directly.
Friends, if you
want to start an insurance advisor business with us, you can clear it by the end of the month.
You'll also find a
link to it in the description, or you'll find our number
directly. You can talk to us directly and ask
how I can generate
income by sending my insurance advisor. During
Corbett's time,
many people lost their jobs and businesses,
but you must have noticed that the health insurance
industry is a separate market for grocery. A
gang of 130-40% is active. By
dividing the entire market, you can also grow your business by
selling health insurance and
advising people. You can earn by
selling the benefits of health insurance to people. I'll
tell you in the final, if you have any questions, please comment.
Now, we'll meet in the next series.
In the video, we
will know about the
benefits of the Aadhar product.
Thank you so much friend. If you have any
question, please comment. Finally, we will meet
in the next video. Thank you so much.